Coming up on Punirunes...
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
The show is squishing!
Punirunes. Before we knew it, these creatures
began to inhabit the human world.
They're squishsterious and soft to the touch!
They all love to be squished.
Sometimes they're kachi-freezy and hard too!
These are some merry, adorable puni-pals.
Who knows, there could be
a Punirune right next to you!
Squishy Squishy Puni Puni
Punirunes♪
"Squishy Squishy Puni Puni Punirunes♪"
Airune
This is Airune, a perky Punirune
full of curiosity.
Enerune
Enerune is energetic.
Loverune
Loverune is full of big love.
Ururune
Ururune is prone to tears
but is great at drawing.
Coolrune
Coolrune is fashionable and tidy.
The Punirunes are full of energy as always.
I think this is gonna come out
super squishy!
What do you think?
I call it the Oden Konjac Bread!
Yuka
Yuka here lives with Airune
and loves all things squishy.
What would that even taste like?
Aoi
Yuka's best friend Aoi lives with Enerune.
Squish contact
This is squish contact.
It's how puni-pals greet each other.
I'm gonna squish you too!
There really is nothing more calming
than squishing.
"It's time!"
Oh yeah. You're all visiting Jewelrune today.
Ururune proposes they go find gifts to bring.
Goodbye!
Have a safe trip!
Now, off to Puniland!
Puniland
This is Puniland, the squishsterious
realm of the Punirunes.
Airune and friends are at the Puni Market
to find gifts for Jewelrune.
Which one will you bring?
They're just for you?!
Ururune and Jewelrune are picking out
a fashionable gift.
Wait a minute.
Are you here to find a gift or what?
Oh, Loverune.
You're just looking for yourself too!
Now, you've found your gifts,
so it's time to go see Jewelrune.
Kachikochiland
This here is Kachikochiland.
Where could Jewelrune's castle be?
"We're pleased by your arrival!
Prince Jewelrune awaits!"
Onwards, to the castle where Jewelrune waits.
Jewelrune
Jewelrune is the prince of Kachikochiland.
"Is it prepared?"
"Let the party begin!"
"Enjoy yourselves!"
"Allow us to perform a dance for you."
The attendants do a kachi-stiff dance!
The attendants do a
kachi-stiff dance!
Ururune does a squishsterious dance!
Ururune does a
squishsterious dance!
"Ahh, that was very fun."
"You can stay as long as you like!"
"I mean it! Stay here forever!"
"Stay here forever!"
"It is our duty to fulfill Jewelrune's wishes."
"You shall remain here in Kachikochiland forever!"
"Now! Service them!"
"Hold on... you all..."
"Halt! We're not done servicing you!"
"You can use this seesaw to jump over the wall!"
However...
All hope is lost!
"I found something odd in the forest."
"But what is it? Pray tell!
What ever could it be?"
"Please investigate!"
"Now's your chance."
"Thanks! See you later!"
"Come play with me again, okay?"
Welcome back! So, did you have fun?
Their journey was full of surprises,
but the Punirunes enjoyed themselves a lot.
Puni-Pal Files!
Today, I'll tell you about...
Airune
Airune!
Airune is a big foodie!
It loves all squishy foods!
And it love-love-loves getting squished itself!
Time for the Puni-Pal Squestion!
What happens to Airune after this?
1. It turns kachi-freezy
2. It turns kara-dry
3. It turns gari-crunchy
Here's the answer!
Here's the answer...
1. It turns kachi-freezy!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Give the squishence a good stir
And make a nice yummy dish
Once they're all full
They look so happy♪
The more that we're together
The more we understand each other
And just like that (Squish! Squish!)
We're best friends (Squish! Squish!)
It's so squishsterious!
Puni!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Next Time
What?! Airune turned into a Babyrune!
S-So cute!
Feeding it...
Next Time
Taking it to the potty...
Taking care of it is so much fun!
Next Time
Next time: "Airune Becomes a Babyrune♪"
Airune
Becomes a Babyrune♪
"Puni" in next time!